RUPESH SHRESTHA

STUDENT/WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT +977 9860672511

rupeshxtha6@gmail.com

 \bigcirc

Chandragiri -12, Kathmandu, Nepal 44600

SKILLS

- HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- MySQL/PHP
- Python
- Django
- WordPress
- Office Handling Package
- Photoshop
- Critical Thinking

EDUCATION

Bachelor In Computer Application

The Times International College

2018 - Present

+2 Computer Science (Management)

Nepalaya College

2016 - 1018

HOBBIES

- Web Development
- Music & Instruments
- Travel

LANGUAGES

- English
- Nepali
- Newari

PROFILE

I am a student of BCA(Bachelor of Computer Application). Detail-oriented and organized and meticulous personnel. Works at fast pace to meet tight deadlines. Experienced Web Developer with passion for creating attractive and interactive website meeting customer needs and exceeding expectations. Well-versed in developing website using Python and Django. Excel in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP development. Enthusiastic team player ready to contribute to company success.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

FEST(Future Education of Science & Technology)

2022-2023

- Design and Development front in UI using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and jQuery.
- Updated and redesigned websites to increase visual appeal, interactivity and user experience.
- Coded websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery and PHP.
- Fixing bugs and errors, designing website layouts, designing, and collaborating on different projects.
- Responsibility for the implementation of Web Design based on HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap & PHP.
- Implemented custom validation controls for various forms with help of JavaScript validation controls.

Web Developer Trainee

2020-2022

Golden Institute Pvt Ltd

- Developing web application using Django Framework.
- Handled development and management of front end user interface with help of HTML, CSS, jQuery and JavaScript.
- Collaborate with other developers, designers, and stakeholders to gather requirements and implement solutions.
- Design and implement models, views, templates, and forms using Django's architecture and best practices.
- Implement user authentication, authorization, and security features in Django applications.
- Optimize Django applications for performance, scalability, and responsiveness.